<Document>
  # GONDOLA-CLASS CRUISE SHUTTLE
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="VendingMachineBooze" Caption="Bar"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Bed" Caption="Lounge"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="FloorWaterEntity" Caption="Pool"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasThermoMachineHeater" Caption="Sauna"/>
  </Box>
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ShuttleMapGondola" Caption=""/>
  </Box>
    [color=#a4885c]Ship Size:[/color] Medium

	[color=#a4885c]Recommended Crew:[/color] 1-4

	[color=#a4885c]Power Gen Type:[/color] Plasma

	[color=#a4885c]Expeditions:[/color] None

	[color=#a4885c]IFF Console:[/color] None

  "A medium-sized space cruise-ship. Sauna with a hot tub, a full bar, a full glass-floor wall-to-wall pool, massive windows for amazing views, and a lounge for variety of activities: it has everything for a romantic getaway."

  [italic]Manufactured by Energy Redistribution Productions.[/italic]

  # PREFLIGHT CHECKLIST

  ## 1. Power supply

  ## 1.1. Battery units
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SMESBasic"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SubstationBasic"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="APCBasic"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that the SMES unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check that the substation unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check that the APC unit's Main Breaker is toggled on.
  - Check the APC unit's current Load* (W).

  ## 1.2. P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="PortableGeneratorPacmanShuttle"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SheetPlasma"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that P.A.C.M.A.N. generator units are anchored to the floor.
  - Check that P.A.C.M.A.N. generator units are fueled. For extended flights make sure that you have enough fuel stockpiled to sustain prolonged power generation.
  - Check that P.A.C.M.A.N. generator units are set to HV output.
  - Start P.A.C.M.A.N. generator units.

  ## 2. Atmospherics

  ## 2.1. Distribution Loop
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="OxygenCanister"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPort"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPressurePump"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that the oxygen and nirogen canisters are anchored to connector port.
  - Check that the distribution pump is set to 101kPa.
  - Check that the distribution loop pump is enabled.

  ## 2.2. Waste Loop
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPressurePump"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AirAlarm"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that the waste loop pump is enabled.

  ## 3. Other checks
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Gyroscope"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GravityGeneratorMini"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that the gyroscope is anchored, powered, and enabled.
  - Check that the mini gravity generator is anchored, powered, and enabled.

  ## Sidenotes

  * - Gondola-class shuttles are intended for recreational flights. To ensure any and all activities on-board are consentual for all participants, it is recommended to avoid the use of mid-shift hiring via crew records console.
</Document>
